var basicQuestions = [
    {
	question: '2 + 2 = ?',
	options: ['seven', 'four', 'five', 'three'],
	answer: ['four'],
    },
    {
	question: '12 - 5 = ?',
	options: ['eight', 'seventeen', 'seven', 'ten'],
	answer: ['seven'],
    },
    {
	question: '10 + 10 = ?',
	options: ['thirtyfive', 'zero', 'ten', 'twenty'],
	answer: ['twenty'],
    },
    {
	question: '15 - 7 = ?',
	options: ['eight', 'twentytwo', 'six', 'eightteen'],
	answer: ['eight'],
    },
    {
	question: '8 + 19 = ?',
	options: ['twenty', 'eleven', 'twentyseven', 'twentytwo'],
	answer: ['twentyseven'],
    },
];

var intermediateQuestions = [
    {
	question: '2 + 2 = ?',
	options: ['seven', 'four', 'five', 'three'],
	answer: ['four'],
    },
    {
	question: '12 - 5 = ?',
	options: ['eight', 'seventeen', 'seven', 'ten'],
	answer: ['seven'],
    },
    {
	question: 'What is the answer to this third question?',
	options: ['This choice', 'This other choice', 'This yet another choice'],
	answer: ['This choice'],
    },
    {
	question: 'What is the answer to this fourth question?',
	options: ['This choice', 'This other choice', 'This yet another choice'],
	answer: ['This choice'],
    },
    {
	question: 'What is the answer to this fifth question?',
	options: ['This choice', 'This other choice', 'This yet another choice'],
	answer: ['This choice'],
    },
];

var advancedQuestions = [
    {
	question: '2 + 2 = ?',
	options: ['seven', 'four', 'five', 'three'],
	answer: ['four'],
    },
    {
	question: '12 - 5 = ?',
	options: ['eight', 'seventeen', 'seven', 'ten'],
	answer: ['seven'],
    },
    {
	question: 'What is the answer to this third question?',
	options: ['This choice', 'This other choice', 'This yet another choice'],
	answer: ['This choice'],
    },
    {
	question: 'What is the answer to this fourth question?',
	options: ['This choice', 'This other choice', 'This yet another choice'],
	answer: ['This choice'],
    },
    {
	question: 'What is the answer to this fifth question?',
	options: ['This choice', 'This other choice', 'This yet another choice'],
	answer: ['This choice'],
    },
];